# Amira Gucher-Blackman

#### Contact

**Address** 

BN20 8JY, Eastbourne

**Phone** 

07913686584

E-mail

amiragucher@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/amira-gucher-blackman-

www

https://github.com/amiragucher

### **Skills**

JavaScript

HTML

CSS

Tailwind

Next Js

React

Postgress

Jest

Node

Postman

**Typescript** 

Heroku

#### **Personal Profile**

Prior to studying at the School of Code my studies evolved around art and design, and then Psychology. During the bootcamp I found a true passion for coding which has only grown over time.

I have experience working with working with people from all walk of life and have gained the ability to work within a team and in an agile frame work. I am an enthusiastic team player ready to contribute to company successes.

# **Recent Experience**

#### School Of Code Graduate May 2022 - August 2022

Recently graduated from the School Of Code bootcamp. During the bootcamp I was introduced to a wide range of programming utilities and languages which has given me the confidence and understanding of a wide variety of areas within tech. I have gained the ability to work within an agile frame work and have experience working within a tight time schedule and under pressure.

- Training in Agile development
- Weekly Hackathons and presentations
- Trained in a range of technologies (as shown in skills section)
- Exprence with leadership and project management
- Experience with working within a team successfully
- Advanced design skills with Figma and Miro

Talk about experience - tech stack - be more specific

Talk about the 4 week project / hackathons

# **Work History**

2020-12 -

Gig Buddies For Good Mental Health

2021-12

- My role included writing blogs about mental health at university
- I also worked with anindividual with mental health challenges

Vercel I would meet up with my gig buddy once a monthand communicate with them regularly. Auth0 2018-07 -**Personal Carer** Figma 2021-06 • I cared for a teenage girl with autism once a Miro week • This role included going out for walks anddoing Cypress activities such as drawing and crafts. **Express** 2020-04 -Warehouse Assistant 2020-08 Old Town Trader • My role involved talking to customers, administration, processing and shipping orders. 2019-05 -Sales Assistant, Artist 2020-01 Anon • This role involved opening and closing the shop, serving customers, managing the shopdisplay and cashing up at the end of the day • I ran the shop on my own. Sales Assistant 2018-07 -2019-08 Jack Wills • My role included interacting with customers as well as cleaning the shop and making sure all the stock is out • I would occasionally work in the stock room dealing with deliveries and stock taking. Volunteer at Jatan Sansthan NGO India 2019-01 -2019-04 International Citizenship Service - ICS • I volunteered in India for three months and worked on three projects including women's health, facilitating youth groups and providing teaching support at a nursery.

## **Education**

2022-04 -	Bootcamp: Software Developer
2022-08	School Of Code - Online
20190 -	University of Brighton
2021-07	I have spent the past two years studyingPsychology
	and Counselling. I have deferred my third year so
	that I can gain work experienceand will be

completing it at a later date.

2018-09 - Brighton Metropolitan College
2019-06 Psychology Access to Higher Education course

2015-09 - BTEC
2017-06 Sussex Downs College
Art and Design

2008-09 - Moira House School
2015-01 including English and Maths.

# **Declaration**

Full, clean driving license
This CV may be kept on file and distributed for
employment purposes
Currently living in Brighton UK, willing to relocate